Collis Potter Huntington Papers
Collis Potter Huntington Papers
- Miscellany
  - Memorabilia
    - Portraits
      - Photographs
        - Collis P. Huntington, by William Keith, 1899; 6 prints, 1 negative (Box 248)
        - Collis P. Huntington, by William Keith, 1899 (Oversize 24)
        - Collis P. Huntington, by William Keith, ca. 1900 (Oversize 24)
      - Photographs, other than C.P.H.
        - New York City, 2 W. 57th St., photo of bedroom suite (Box 248)
        - Pine Knot, undated; 2 prints (Box 248)
        - Pine Knot ?, undated; 4 mounted prints (Box 248)
        - Unidentified, undated (probably 1872-1873); by Watkins' Yosemite Art Gallery (Box 248)
    - Program of memorial service for Collis P. Huntington, San Francisco, Aug. 17, 1900 (Box 248)
    - Resolutions of appreciation, 1883; undated (Box 248)
    - Report card of C. W. Huntington, 1872 (Box 248)
  - Other
    - Holstein-Friesian Assoc. of America, 1882; 1884-1886; registry and transfer certificates (Box 248)
    - Maps, undated (Box 248)
    - Open letter to the President of the United States re. political situation in California from Edward Curtis, Apr. 15, 1885 (Box 248)
    - Recipe for Russian remedy for consequences of the grippe, undated (Box 248)
    - Specifications and accoutrements for railroad car Oneonta, 1883; 1887-1888,; 1892 (Box 248)
    - Specifications of sea-going steam yacht, 1886 (Box 248)
    - Speech delivered on behalf of Collis P. Huntington, Durango, Mexico, holo, Nov. 1, 1892 (Box 248)
    - Transportation references and memoranda from files of New York Tribune, 1875-1902 (Box 248)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 248)
  - Printed material
    - "Address of C. P. Huntington before the Committee on Pacific Railroads of the House of Representatives." Volume 334, March 12, 1896 (Box 248)
    - "The Central Pacific Railroad Company in Equitable Account with the U.S.: Review of Testimony and Exhibits Presented Before the Pacific Railway Commission." Volume 335, 1887 (Box 248)
    - "Central Pacific Settlement: Letters from J. C. Stubbs to C. P. H." Volume 336, 1896 (Box 248)
    - Circulars, etc., 1875-1897; undated (Box 248)
    - Circulars re. the Funding Bill, 1896 (Box 248)
    - "Debate on the Pacific Railroad Funding Bill, Delivered in the House of Representatives." Volume 337, January 7, 8, 9, and 11, 1897 (Box 248)
    - "How Congressmen are Bribed: The Colton Letters." Volume 338, 1896 (Box 248)
    - "The Railways and the United States Land Office," by Henry Beard, 1883 (Box 249)
    - "Remarks of Hon. James G. Maguire Before H. R. Committee on Pacific Railroads, .", June 4, 1894 (Box 249)
    - "Report of Discussion Between the House and Senate Committees on Pacific Railroads and C. P. Huntington.", January 23-24, 1890 (Box 249)
    - Speech "Our Country" by C. P. Huntington, May 13, 1899 (Box 249)
    - "The Texas Pacific Railway Contrasted with a Real Southern Pacific Railroad by Thomas Norwood, 1878 (Box 249)
    - "Thirty-Second Parallel Pacific Railroad. Remarks of C. P. Huntington Before the Committee on the Pacific Railroads.", Jan. 31, 1878 (Box 249)
    - "Transcript of Hearings Before Senate Committee on the Pacific Railroads." (Volumes 345, 346), 1896 (Box 249)
    - "Views of the Minority of H.R. Committees on the Pacific Railroad." (Volume 347), Apr 27, 1896 (Box 249)
  - Duplicates
    - Clippings (Box 249)
    - Printed material (Box 249)
    - Receipts and bills (Box 249)
    - Re. Africa (Box 249)
    - Unidentified notes (Box 249)
  - Weeds
    - Miscellaneous material weeded from collection, 9 folders (Box 249)
  - Indexes
    - Subject headings (A-L, Ma-Z), 2 boxes index cards (Box 250)
    - Index (A-D, E-Ho), 2 boxes index cards (Box 250)
    - Index (Hu-Mc, M-Sp, St-Z), 3 boxes index cards (Box 251)